{
    "subject": "resource/Rome2rio",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundedBy",
    "object": "resource/Bernhard_Tschirren",
    "human_readable": "Rome2rio was founded by Bernhard Tschirren.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9123184680938721,
            "question": "Who founded Rome2rio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7981846928596497,
            "question": "What year was Rome2rio founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6733344793319702,
            "question": "Who developed the concept behind Rome2rio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600287914276123,
            "question": "What is Bernhard Tschirren known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5575839877128601,
            "question": "What company did Bernhard Tschirren found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4870881140232086,
            "question": "What are some of the features offered by Rome2rio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2754288911819458,
            "question": "Is Rome2rio a popular travel resource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2588433027267456,
            "question": "What type of service does Rome2rio provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2049304097890854,
            "question": "Is Rome2rio a travel planning platform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15662652254104614,
            "question": "Does Rome2rio offer transportation information?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rome2rio was founded by Bernhard Tschirren.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7450_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Rome2rio a travel planning platform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7450_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of service does Rome2rio provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7450_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Rome2rio a popular travel resource?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7450_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7450_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that according to the context information, it is mentioned that \"Rome2rio is a multi-modal travel search site founded by Michael Cameron and Bernhard Tschirren in 2010\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7450/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt) and also \"Rome2rio is a Melbourne start-up founded in 2010 by two former Microsoft engineers, Dr Michael Cameron and Bernhard Tschirren\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7450/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt). This supports the triple that Rome2rio was founded by Bernhard Tschirren."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Rome2rio was founded by Bernhard Tschirren.\" Specifically, multiple sources mention that Rome2rio was co-founded by Bernhard Tschirren and Michael Cameron."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}